<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on moravek.me</title>
    <link>https://moravek.me/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on moravek.me</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.145.0</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 21:56:44 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://moravek.me/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Departure Board on Led Matrix Display</title>
      <link>https://moravek.me/posts/departure-board-on-led-matrix-display/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 21:56:44 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://moravek.me/posts/departure-board-on-led-matrix-display/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Recently I saw a cool project someone shared on the ESPHome Discord server that inspired me and I&amp;rsquo;ve decided that I&amp;rsquo;ll attempted to replicate it and build something similar. It was a LED matrix display based departure board connected to an Arduino that was displaying publicly available information about upcoming departures of the nearest public transport stop.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Since I live in Prague where we happen to have a publicly available data where you can fetch live information about location of trams/buses/metro and their delays I thought it should be pretty much doable. The public transport APIs are available at &lt;a href=&#34;https://api.golemio.cz/docs/openapi/index.htm&#34;&gt;Golemio API&lt;/a&gt;, you must register to get your API Key and then you&amp;rsquo;re good to go. The default rate-limit policies are pretty generous and completely sufficient for this home project.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LaskaKit E-Paper Kit With Home Assistant</title>
      <link>https://moravek.me/posts/laskakit-epaper-kit-with-home-assistant/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 20:56:48 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://moravek.me/posts/laskakit-epaper-kit-with-home-assistant/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This is just a note to future self on how I made the LaskaKit E-Paper Kit work with Home Assistant and ESPHome.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Just a bit of context: The &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.laskakit.cz/laskakit-live-7-5-e-paper-stavebnice-s-wifi-pro---zivy-obraz-/?variantId=13529&#34;&gt;kit&lt;/a&gt; I got my hands on contains a E-Paper display and a custom ESP32-based board called ESPink which also comes pre-flashed with a custom firmware. You can build a firmware for this board yourself and the code is available in &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/LaskaKit/ESPink&#34;&gt;GitHub&lt;/a&gt;. However I wasn&amp;rsquo;t interested in running the board with this custom FW as I wanted to connect it with my local Home Assistant instance.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My First Post</title>
      <link>https://moravek.me/posts/my-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 21:50:50 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://moravek.me/posts/my-first-post/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hello World!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
